Levi Magnus

Coldstream, British Columbia, Canada | levi.magnus@alumni.ubc.ca | 250-938-4519 | levimagnus.ca

OVERVIEW

Highly motivated computer science graduate with a passion for creating quality software. Strong communication and programming skills, as well as previous experience working on a variety of projects, will help me excel at your company.

EDUCATION

University of British Columbia, Kelowna, BC

2015 - 2020

Bachelor of Science - Major in Computer Science, Minor in Data Science Academic Average – 86.5% Deputy Vice-Chancellor Scholarship for Academic Achievement

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department of Computer Science, UBCO (Kelowna, BC) Mobile Application Developer in Assistive Technologies

September, 2019 - April, 2020

- Sole developer of an augmented reality guidance application intended for use with Android mobile devices and head-mounted displays to aid in a research project
- Developed using Unity, the Vuforia Engine, and the C# programming language

UBC Okanagan Centre for Teaching and Learning (Kelowna, BC) Learning Technologies Rover

January, 2019 - May, 2019

- Supported faculty and staff in the use of various technologies that enhance teaching and learning
- Solved issues that arose with any of the learning technologies on campus
- Helped faculty design engaging online courses including custom course pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

UBC Centre for Teaching, Learning and Technology (Vancouver, BC)

May, 2018 - December, 2018

Canvas Technology Rover

- Redesigned the UBCO Canvas support website to meet W3C standards and improve the user experience, resulting in increased traffic to the site and positive user feedback
- Worked with the UBC Canvas API User Community to develop, test, document and maintain Python scripts that added to existing Canvas functionality and integrated the platform with other tools used at UBC
- Provided Canvas support and training to faculty and staff in the form of written documentation, one-on-one consultations, and workshop presentations

Church of God of Prophecy – Western Canada (Vernon, BC) Web Designer

February, 2017 - April, 2017

- Worked closely with the clientele to gather the requirements for the website and plan out the design
- Customized the structure and appearance of the website using HTML and CSS
- Used a content management system (WordPress) so the clientele could easily run a blog

PROJECTS

Augmented Reality Messaging Application

September, 2019 - April, 2020

Developed for Saturn Animation Studios Inc.

- Developed an AR messaging app with a small team of developers using React Native, TypeScript, Node.is, and Firebase
- Agile development methodology was used alongside tools like Jira and AWS CodeCommit

Community Forum Website

February, 2018 - April, 2018

- Built a dynamic and responsive website where users can view, share, and post various content
- Tech stack included HTML5, CSS3, JS, PHP, and MySQL